

My Contact

ranjayprasad65@gmail.com

+91 7379529084

Deoria, Uttar Pradesh

Portfolio Link Click me

Hard Skill

- Web Design and Development

Soft Skill

- Decision making Communication
- Multi-tasking

Education Background

- Persuing from ITM maharajganj, Currently in
- Completed Bachelor of Art from IGNOU Distance Learning , New Delhi from 2020 to 2023
- Diploma in Information Technology
- Class 12th

Ranjay Kr Prasad

Web Developer | Animation | Design | Display Ads | Campaign

About Me

I worked on Making eye-catching Design and Campaign for Different Platform Like DCS, DCM, DV360 also User Research, Visual design, Digital Banners. Designed Website layouts, templates and cool branded branded looks.

Worked with clients to gather and define requirements, establish scopes and managing project milestones.

Working Experiences

Digilakshya Service Pvt Ltd, Gurgaon Oct 2021 till now Haryana

Professional Experience

Web Design and Dev. @Digilakshya Service Pvt Ltd 2023 till now

Key responsibilities:

- · Design Websites and Dev using HTML CSS, JS
- Animated GIFs for Web
- Banner Animation for Advertisement
- · Making visual and Development for Website and Conversion PSDs or Figma to HTML

Digital Banner Ads, 2D animation @Digilakshya Service Pvt Ltd.

2021 till now

Key responsibilities:

- · As per clients requirments, or input file given by clients we have ot
- · Making Design and layouts More Professional good looking
- Desgined banner for DCM, DCS, DV360

UI UX Design @Digilakshya Service Pvt Ltd 2023 till now

Key responsibilities:

- Designing Website Layouts
- · Designing eye-catching Display Ads Banner